issuu.com 2019-06-30

# Privacy Policy - Issuu

**Last Updated: July 28th, 2015**

**PLEASE NOTE: The Issuu Privacy Policy is effective as of the "Last Updated" date above. (Seehere for the previous version of the Privacy Policy.)**

Issuu, Inc. operates the Issuu service and related services, applications, domains and networks offered by Issuu ("Issuu Service"). The Issuu Service allows you to connect, collaborate, share, and remix documents with other users of the Issuu Service community on the Internet. Issuu’s Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use your information. By using or accessing the Issuu Service, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of the policy. We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy whenever you access the Issuu Service to stay informed about our information practices. 

##  Information Gathered by Issuu 

This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of “personally identifiable” information (meaning it can be used to specifically identify you as a unique person) or “non-personally identifiable” information (meaning it cannot be used to specifically identify you) that we may collect in your use of the Issuu Service. We use both types of information, and combinations of both types. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of any other company or individual that we do not own or control. 

**Visitors:** For visitors to our website and registered users, we log certain information, such as your IP address, browser type and usage data, for example, how much time you spent reading, which publications you read, and which pages you accessed. In addition, if you access the Issue Service via our mobile application, we also collect mobile device IDS such as IDFA (iOS) and Android ID. 

**Registration:** If you choose to register with us, Issuu may ask you to provide your name, email address and physical address. Issuu also asks each user to create an account ID and password. Issuu may ask you to provide demographic information, such as age, gender, interests or occupation to enhance our ability to provide a more personalized experience for users. We may also, via a third party service, collect credit card information for any paid services or purchases. 

**Feedback and Chat:** We may collect other information when you provide feedback or comments or communicate with others through our systems. 

**Info through other services:** You may give us permission to collect your information in other services. For example, you may create an account via a social networking service ("SNS") such as Facebook, Google Plus or Twitter . When you do this, it allows us to obtain information from those accounts (for example, your friends or contacts) either automatically in accordance with their terms or as a result of your selections in the SNS. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons:** Issuu uses "cookies" – small files containing a string of characters sent to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser – in addition to Flash shared browser objects to administer its website and provide a more tailored and user-friendly service to you. For example, we may use cookies or Flash objects to count the number of unique computers accessing our website. You can set your browser to refuse cookies from the Issuu Service if you choose. When you access the Issuu Service or open one of our HTML emails, we may automatically record certain information from your system by using different types of tracking technology. This "automatically collected" information may include IP Address, a unique ID, version of software installed, system type, the content and pages that you access on the Issuu Service, and the dates and times that you visit the Issuu Service. You can usually instruct your browser, by changing its settings, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Issuu Service or all functionality of the Issuu Service. 

##  Information Gathered by Third Party Analytics Services and Ad Networks 

We may let other companies use cookies, web beacons, and other technologies such as software development kits in the Issuu Service. These companies may collect information such as unique device identifiers, IP address, geolocation, OS information, and user activity. For example, we work with third parties, such as Flurry Inc., to provide analytics information regarding your use of the Issuu Service. For more information about Flurry's privacy practices, please visit [here](http://www.flurry.com/legal-privacy/privacy-policy-updated). To opt-out of Flurry Analytics tracking used with the issuu iOS mobile application visit [this site](http://www.flurry.com/legal-privacy/end-user-opt-out). 

Some of the advertisements you see on the Issuu Service are delivered by advertisers or through ad networks which collect information about you and your activities through the use of cookies, web beacons, and other technologies. These advertisers or ad networks may include, but are not limited to Google AdSense, MoPub, Criteo, AdRoll, VelisMedia, SayMedia and Q1Media. The use of cookies, web beacons, and other technologies by these companies is subject to the privacy policies of those third parties. Some of these companies are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) or Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”), each of which offers a single location to opt out of receiving tailored ads from its member companies. To opt out of information collection by NAI member companies, or to obtain information about the technologies they use or their own privacy policies, please visit the NAI consumer opt out page located at: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. To opt out of information collection by DAA member companies, or to obtain information about the technologies they use or their own privacy policies, please visit the DAA consumer opt out page located at: <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>. Mobile device operating system software such as Apple iOS and Google Play Services provide an opt-out choice e.g., Limit Ad Tracking on iOS. To opt-out, the User should consult the User’s device settings. 

##  Payment Card Information 

To use certain aspects of the Issuu Service, we may require credit or debit card account information. By submitting your credit or debit card account information through the Issuu Service, you expressly consent to the sharing of your information with third party merchants, subscription and billing processors, and payment processors. These third parties may store your credit or debit card account information so you can use the Issuu Service in the future. We transmit your credit or debit card account information to these third parties, but do not store such information. We cannot guarantee that transmissions of your credit or debit card account information will always be secure or that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat the security measures taken by us or our third-party service providers. We assume no liability or responsibility for disclosure of your information due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third-party access, or other causes beyond our control. 

##  Issuu Uses of Information 

We may use information we collect about you as follows: 

  * To provide and improve the Issuu Service. 
  * To customize the Issuu Service and provide advertisements, content or features that match your interests. 
  * To permit our users to set up an account. 
  * To respond to your comments, questions and requests and provide customer service. 
  * To send you notices, updates, security alerts and other administrative messages. 
  * To communicate with you about products, services, offers and events offered by Issuu and others. 
  * To process transactions and send you related information. 
  * To link or combine with information we get from others to help provide you with better service. 
  * To detect, investigate and/or prevent fraudulent, unauthorized or illegal activity. 
  * To diagnose problems with the Issuu Service. 
  * To analyze and monitor how users utilize the Issuu Service. 
  * To carry out other purposes for which the information was collected. 

##  When Issuu Discloses Information 

Issuu does not share your personally identifiable information, including any of your user profile data that you create, with other organizations for their marketing or promotional uses. Please be aware, however, that 1) any personally identifiable information that you voluntarily choose to display on the Issuu Service becomes publicly available and may be collected and used by others without restriction; and 2) as a feature of the Issuu Service, other users may become aware of your behavior or document viewing activities to their own profile pages and may use this information without restriction. 

Issuu may share personally identifiable information about our users with third parties, including: (a) with your consent or as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy; (b) when we believe it is necessary pursuant to a subpoena or other judicial or administrative order; (c) where required by law; (d) to enforce or apply our Privacy Policy, our Terms of Service or our other policies or agreements; (e) at our sole discretion, where we deem necessary to respond to claims, to protect the safety of any individual or the public, or to protect the rights or property of the Issuu Service or any third party or (f) in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition, or in any other situation where personally identifiable information may be disclosed or transferred as one of our business assets. We may disclose personally identifiable information to (i) affiliated companies or (ii) vendors, service providers or other partners who support our business such as providing web site hosting, maintenance, and security services; fulfilling orders; conducting data analysis and creating reports; offering certain functionality, including but not limited to serving advertisements; offering customer service support; and assisting Issuu in improving the Issuu Service and creating new service features. Issuu may also disclose anonymous or aggregated user information to third parties. 

##  Changing or Deleting Your Information 

You have the ability to modify your account-specific information, through the edit function on your profile. If you wish to deactivate your Issuu Service account, you may do so. Removed information such as your account ID, geolocation information connected to your user ID, and any documents that you have uploaded to the Issuu Service may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time. In addition, we may retain certain information as required by law, for legitimate business purposes, or as part of our regular retention practices. We may also retain cached or archived copies of information about you. 

##  Data Security 

Issuu will use commercially reasonable efforts to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. However, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you provide to us or guarantee that information on the Issuu Service may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by unauthorized persons.. 

##  International Transfer 

Your information may be transferred to and maintained on computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. For example, if you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to us, your personal information may be transferred to the United States and processed there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer. 

##  Children Under 13 

IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE ISSUU SERVICE AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER. 

The Issuu Service is not directed to children under 13. Issuu does not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13, please do not use the Issuu Service or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 who has become a member of the Issuu Service, then please contact Issuu at privacy@issuu.com to have that child's account terminated and information deleted. 

##  Web Browser “Do Not Track” Notice 

We currently do not participate in any "Do Not Track" (“DNT”) frameworks that would allow us to respond to signals or other mechanisms from you regarding the collection of your information. Your DNT settings, however, may affect third party services we may use. 

##  Contacting Issuu 

Please contact Issuu with any questions at: 

> Issuu, Inc.  
> 131 Lytton Ave  
> Palo Alto, CA 94301  
> USA 

Or by email: [privacy@issuu.com](mailto:privacy@issuu.com)
